{
    "id": "a7384317321a4395b445cc780361698b",
    "title": "Prepositions By, With, To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was red ……………………….. embarrassment.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which show how people are showing their emotions and sensations. ",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e8cc3b3611a4216a4234b0be14fa992"
        },
        {
            "question": "The travelers were shivering ……………………. cold.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which show how people are showing their emotions and sensations. ",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0dfae512950444d59fd53416e95233db"
        },
        {
            "question": "I drew their attention ………………………. shouting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "040f70bc28824a538e1b71e9ca4d9d1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should reach there ………………………. 5 o’clock.",
            "description": "By can mean not later than.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "within"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e27ed1114a1448b9db47849386ee7c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… the end of the party, everybody was tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By",
                "With",
                "To"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec14d32dfa314ee1bff26424045b94fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "He succeeded ……………………… hard work.",
            "description": "We use by to talk about what we do to get a certain result. We use with to talk about what we use to get a result. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cefb30d6758f47ebadca26175883f9ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our roof was damaged ………………………. the storm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab6bb7ea9b0e45488760d411dae7e8e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was interrogated ……………………….. the police inspector.",
            "description": "In passive voice, by is used to introduce the agent.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4b6309b9e0b04c259776a97b3e1ad4c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earned just enough to get ……………………….",
            "description": "To get by is to survive with great difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e64d30aae054b4d86cbe07dc6834a7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please be patient …………………….. the children.",
            "description": "With is used after several adjectives which show how people are feeling towards others.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b8bc05634b74a0eacd17f4355093c52"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has always been nice …………………….. me.",
            "description": "With is not used with words like kind, polite, nice, rude etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7219a09afccd425692c21877eee11045"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are so many people ……………………….. no homes.",
            "description": "With indicates possession. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6e734bdfe054fd4bf60a16685696c4c"
        }
    ]
}